Jong-Won Park

+82 10 8239-8237 jejeoppa@naver.com

Smart factory engineer equipped with experience in TIC (Testing, Inspection, Certification) industry. Employs excellent communication skills and detailed personalbility. Experience in development of testing process like test cases and test software, training as a trainer, diverse certificate project



Experience

02/2020 to current

Smart Factory Engineer

TUV SUD Korea, Seoul

- Responsibility for IEC 62541, IEC 62443, SQA Certificate
- IEC 62541 (OPC UA) Interoperability certificate process development
- Automation test program, test case development
- Tested and certified as a project handler for KETI IEC 62541 certificate
- Tested and certified as a project handler for Mintit SQA software quality functionality certificate

03/2019 to 08/2019

Embedded system education based on IoT (Education)

Korea Chamber of Commerce and Industry

- Linux OS(kernel, device driver)
- Android application
- Firmware programing(Arduino, Atmega, ARM)
- TCP/IP socket communication

06/2018 to 08/2018

Embedded system education (Education)

Robot SW educational institution

- ARM processor programming
- Robot system programming
- Mobile robot project

Highlights

- OPC UA Education
- Certify for OPC UA product, SQA (Software Quality Assurance), Cybersecurity
- Knowledge of Embedded systems
- Computer language: C, C++, JAVA

Education

03/2013 to 02/2019 Bachelor of Robotics, Kwangwoon University, seoul

License

- ISA/IEC 62443
 Cybersecurity Funamentals
 Specialist
- ISA/IEC 62443
 Cybersecurity Risk
 Assessment Specialist
- KS Q ISO/IEC 17025 Operation
- Estimation of measurement uncertainty
- TOEIC Speaking LV6 (150)